<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="help_intro">The following actions may be accessible from the different Tolomet
        activities:
    </string>
    <string name="help_favorite">Adds or removes the selected station to the favorite list. This
        is a convenient way for accessing quickly the most visited stations, and it is also
        mandatory for using the station in a widget.
    </string>
    <string name="help_refresh">Updates the current content. In the case of the charts activity it
        tries to download a new reading from the server. If the time elapsed from the last reading
        is too little, the user is just warned in order to minimize server traffic.
    </string>
    <string name="help_charts">This is the default activity. It shows an spinner to chose a
        station, and different charts are displayed according to user settings (experiment with
        <i>simple</i> and <i>full</i> display modes to chose the one you like the most). You can
        also scroll to check previous readings of the day or even readings from past days (only
        if the meteo provider supports access to this history).
    </string>
    <string name="help_info">Shows details of the station selected. An embedded browser shows
        the station details on the provider web site.</string>
    <string name="help_map"><![CDATA[
        Shows a map with the closest stations. You can change the current
        station both using the spinner or navigating in the map. Each station is shown using a
        marker with a <font color="#008800">green</font>, <font color="#888800">yellow</font> or
        <font color="#880000">red</font> color depending on the update rate of the station
        provider. In the case you zoom out too much, the stations are collapsed by regions
        (in <font color="#4A2364">purple</font>) or by countries
        (in <font color="#000088">blue</font>).
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_origin">Shows the readings of the station selected in the provider\'s
        web site using an embedded browser. This is useful in case the charts activity tells
        that there is not data available and you want to confirm whether there it is a fault of
        the provider web site or of Tolomet. In this last case you can opt to report the failure
        using the report action described below. This activity is also useful in case you want
        to check other type of readings not available from the charts activity.
    </string>
    <string name="help_browser">This is the same as the previous action but using an external web
        browser instead of the one embedded in Tolomet. This is useful if you want to bookmark the
        URL in the web browser or to use other features. Please note that some providers
        (i.e. Euskalmet) shows different results depending on whether you are using a browser in
        a mobile phone or in a desktop PC. In this case you should use a browser that has the option
        to view the website as in a PC.
    </string>
    <string name="help_share">It allows to easily share the view of the current Tolomet activity
        with other users using an application selected from a list. Typically both a screenshot and
        a default text message is provided by Tolomet.
    </string>
    <string name="help_whatsapp">The same as the previous action but using WhatsApp directly
        instead of asking for the application to be used to share the content.
    </string>
    <string name="help_fly">Changes between flying and landed modes. When in flight mode the screen
        is always on and the rotation is disabled. This only affects to Tolomet, not to other apps
        in the phone. In this mode the readings are automatically updated using the provider\'s
        update rate or each minute in case the reading is delayed.
    </string>
    <string name="help_settings">This allows to customize the experience with Tolomet, modifying
        its view, such as the type of charts displayed or the scaling of the axes, and its
        behaviour, such as the criteria used to download new readings.
    </string>
    <string name="help_report">This action allows you to easily give me a feedback of your
        experience with Tolomet: bug reports, new feature requests, offer yourself to translate
        Tolomet to another language or invite me to fly with you ;). It opens a mail client with a
        default subject and a body. Please add your message to the mail body, but do not remove the
        original body since it contains technical information which can help me to improve Tolomet
        for your specific device type.
    </string>
    <string name="help_widget"><![CDATA[
        The widget allows you to have a quick look at your favorite spot(s) from the home screen.
        There are three widget sizes available, displaying more or less information. When you add a
        widget, a configuration screen is opened to allow you to customize which are your preferred
        flying conditions at a given spot using any of the stations in your favorite list. The
        preferred wind direction range is specified with two values in degrees (between 0 and 360):
        <u>from</u> and <u>to</u>. For instance the pair [from=0, to=90] would indicate that all
        winds between north and east are fine to fly, and the pair [from=270, to=90] would indicate
        that all winds with a north component (both west and east) are fine. The icon of the widget
        is shown in <font color="#880000">red</font> if any of the readings are not within your
        preferred flying conditions, in <font color="#888800">yellow</font> if there is no
        information available or the conditions are in a transition from bad to good, and in
        <font color="#008800">green</font> if the flying conditions are good during the last two
        readings. If you click on the icon, the readings are updated (if necessary), and if you
        click on the text, Tolomet is opened showing the readings of the corresponding station.
        ]]>
    </string>
</resources>